{
    "subject": "resource/Edinho_Campos",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Niter\u00f3i",
    "human_readable": "Edinho Campos was born in Niter\u00f3i.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.90140300989151,
            "question": "Where was Edinho Campos born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44883376359939575,
            "question": "Is Edinho Campos from Brazil?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36000290513038635,
            "question": "Could Edinho Campos have been a famous athlete?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3471469581127167,
            "question": "What is Niter\u00f3i known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33072999119758606,
            "question": "Is there a famous landmark in Niter\u00f3i?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3199618458747864,
            "question": "Are there any other famous people from Niter\u00f3i?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24868887662887573,
            "question": "What is the population of Niter\u00f3i?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24034203588962555,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about Niter\u00f3i?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19061322510242462,
            "question": "What are some popular tourist attractions in Niter\u00f3i?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15088951587677002,
            "question": "What kind of climate does Niter\u00f3i have?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Edinho Campos was born in Niter\u00f3i.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3393_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular tourist attractions in Niter\u00f3i?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3393_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some interesting facts about Niter\u00f3i?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3393_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the population of Niter\u00f3i?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3393_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3393_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3393_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3393_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3393_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3393_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3393_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3393_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3393_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3393_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3393_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all four documents mention that Edinho was born in Niter\u00f3i, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil. \n\nDocument 1: \"Edinho was born on January 15, 1983, in Niter\u00f3i, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil.\"\n\nDocument 2: \"According to the data we have Edimo Ferreira Campos, better known as Edinho, was born on January 15, 1983 in the city of Niter\u00f3i, Brasil.\"\n\nDocument 3: No mention of birthplace for this person.\n\nDocument 4: No mention of this person's name is related to Edinho Campos, but another person Edinho with a different birthdate and place (Rio de Janeiro)"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Edimo Ferreira Campos, better known as Edinho, was born on January 15, 1983, in Niter\u00f3i, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil. Therefore, the statement \"Edinho Campos was born in Niter\u00f3i\" is supported by the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}